Irving Berlin Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Show Music (Box 1-219)
  - Face the music, Stage, 1932; Earlier titles: Off the beat; This town of ours; Curtain going up
    - Scores and parts
      - Orchestral parts
        - Trombone (Box-folder 100/3)
        - Banjo (Box-folder 100/4)
        - Piano (Box-folder 101/1)
        - Piano, extra parts (Box-folder 101/2)
        - Drums (Box-folder 101/3)
        - Miscellaneous
          - Extra part book, various parts, not used (Box-folder 101/4)
          - Miscellaneous orchestral parts, Torch song (old) (Box-folder 101/5)
          - Manuscript parts (12), Incomplete (Box-folder 101/5)
    - Scripts
      - Carbon copy of typed script; [65] p., Blue folder; On cover: Act I, Oct. 30, 1931 (Box-folder 102/1)
      - Typed script; [41] p., Yellow folder; On cover: Act II (Box-folder 102/1)
      - Photocopy of typed script; [112] p., No folder; Acts I and II (final version) (Box-folder 102/2)
      - Photocopy of typed script; [106] p., No folder; Next-to-last version, some Act II scenes not completed (Box-folder 102/3)
      - Carbon copies of typed script; [72] p. each, 2 copies in yellow folder; On cover: Off the beat, Act I (Box-folder 102/4)
      - Photocopy of manuscript script by Moss Hart; [240] p. approx., Unbound; On t.p.: Off the beat (Box-folder 103/1)
      - Carbon copy of typed script; 57 p., Yellow folder, stapled; Original title on cover: Curtain going up (Box-folder 103/2)
      - Carbon copy of typed script; 177 p., Yellow folder; On cover: 2, This town of ours (Box-folder 103/3)
      - Carbon copy of typed script; [44] p., Yellow folder; At top: 2 (Box-folder 103/4)
      - Carbon copy of typed script; [43] p., Yellow folder; At top: 4 (Box-folder 103/4)
  - Facts and fables, Script by Milton H. Gropper. Idea suggested by Irving Berlin
    - Typed script; [12] p. (Box-folder 219/22)
  - Follow the crowd see Stop! Look! Listen!
  - Follow the fleet, Film, 1936
    - Bound printed piano-vocal score; 29 p. (Box-folder 104/1)
    - But where are you?
      - Manuscript piano-vocal scores; [2, 1] p. (Box-folder 104/2)
      - Manuscript piano scores; [2] p. (Box-folder 104/2)
      - Sketch; [1] p., On verso: sketch for "I'd rather lead a band" (Box-folder 104/2)
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 104/2)
      - Photocopy of manuscript piano-vocal score; [1] p. (Box-folder 104/2)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 104/2)
    - Get thee behind me, Satan
      - Manuscript piano score; [2] p. (Box-folder 104/3)
      - Manuscript piano score; [2] p., With annotations (Box-folder 104/3)
      - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 104/3)
      - Sketches(3); [2] p. each (Box-folder 104/3)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [6] leaves (Box-folder 104/3)
    - I'd rather lead a band
      - Manuscript piano score; [1] p. (Box-folder 104/4)
      - Photocopy of piano-vocal score; [4] p. (Box-folder 104/4)
      - Photocopy of sketch; [1] p., Copied from verso: But where are you? (Box-folder 104/4)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 104/4)
    - I'm puttin' all my eggs in one basket
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 104/5)
    - Let yourself go
      - Manuscript piano score; [1] leaf (Box-folder 104/6)
      - Sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder 104/6)
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 104/6)
      - Photocopy of piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 104/6)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 104/6)
    - Let's face the music and dance
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [1] p. (Box-folder 104/7)
      - Manuscript piano-solo scores; [3, 1] p. (Box-folder 104/7)
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 104/7)
      - Photocopy of piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 104/7)
      - Photocopy of sketch; [1] p., Copied from verso of While we're dancing (Box-folder 104/7)
      - Typescript and carbon copy lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 104/7)
    - Moonlight maneuvers see Non-show music
    - There's a smile on my face see Non-show music
    - We saw the sea
      - Photocopy of piano-vocal score; [5] p. (Box-folder 104/8)
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript of piano-vocal score; 8 p. (Box-folder 104/8)
      - Manuscript vocal part; [1] p. (Box-folder 104/8)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 104/8)
    - Unidentified sketches; [4] p. (Box-folder 104/9)
  - Friar's folic of 1911
    - Songwriters (Box-folder 104/10)
      - Holograph lyric sheets; [2] leaves, At top: Piano bugs
      - Holograph lyric sheets; [3] leaves, At top: Songwriters
  - Good gulf program, 1934
    - I never had a chance see Non-show music
    - In that first revue
      - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 104/11)
    - Say it with music see Non-show music
    - So help me see Non-show music
  - Hanky panky
    - Opera burlesque, Introduced as "The ragtime sextette" in A night with the Pierrots; curtain raiser Whirl of society and sung in Weber and Field's All Star Jubilee Production Hanky Panky, 1912; Alternate titles: Ragtime opera (Lucia); The ragtime sextette; Opera Burlesque (On the Sextette from Lucia di Lammermoor)
      - Manuscript score; 16 p. (Box-folder 104/12)
      - Negative photocopy of printed piano-vocal score; 14 p. (Box-folder 104/12)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [6] leaves (Box-folder 104/12)
  - Happy holidays see Holiday inn
  - Holiday inn, Film, 1942
    - Abraham
      - Manuscript piano score; [2] p. (Box-folder 105/1)
      - Sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder 105/1)
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 105/1)
      - Printed piano-vocal score(2); [4] p. each (Box-folder 105/1)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [9] leaves (Box-folder 105/1)
    - Be careful, it's my heart
      - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal scores(2); [2] p. each (Box-folder 105/2)
      - Sketch of piano score; [2] p. (Box-folder 105/2)
      - Sketch; [1] p., Laid in: typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 105/2)
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p. (Box-folder 105/2)
      - Photocopy of copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 2 p. (Box-folder 105/2)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [16] leaves (Box-folder 105/2)
      - Sheet music (Box-folder 105/2)
    - Finale
      - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 105/3)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [6] leaves (Box-folder 105/3)
    - The fourth of July vocal routine, Includes "Let's say it with firecrackers" and "Song of freedom"
      - Photocopies of condensed score(2); [12] p. each, At top: rec. version (Box-folder 105/4)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [5] leaves (Box-folder 105/4)
    - Happy holiday
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p. (Box-folder 105/5)
      - Photocopies of piano-vocal score(2); [1] p. each (Box-folder 105/5)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 105/5)
    - Happy holiday - opening chorus
      - Part I
        - Photocopies of piano-vocal score(2); 4 p. each (Box-folder 105/6)
        - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 105/6)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [11] leaves, Some with holograph annotations (Box-folder 105/6)
      - Part II
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [8] leaves, Some with holograph annotations (Box-folder 105/6)
    - Holiday inn
      - Manuscript piano score; [2] p. (Box-folder 105/7)
    - I can't tell a lie
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p., Laid in: manuscript piano-vocal fragment; [1] p. (Box-folder 105/8)
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 105/8)
      - Manuscript piano sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 105/8)
      - Sketch of lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 105/8)
      - Photocopies of manuscript piano-vocal score(2); 3 p. each (Box-folder 105/8)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [8] leaves (Box-folder 105/8)
    - I pledge allegiance
      - Manuscript piano-vocal scores(2); [2] p. each (Box-folder 105/9)
      - Manuscript piano score; [1] p. (Box-folder 105/9)
      - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 105/9)
      - Photocopies of manuscript piano-vocal scores(2); 3 p. each (Box-folder 105/9)
    - I remember Christmas time, Duet sung in counterpoint with White Christmas
      - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 105/10)
      - Manuscript vocal score; [2] p. (Box-folder 105/10)
      - Photocopy of typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 105/10)
    - I'll capture your heart singing, Original title: Sing and dance; Film version: I'll capture her heart singing
      - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 105/11)
      - Photocopy of short score; 6 p., Laid in: typescript interoffice note; [1] p. (Box-folder 105/11)
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p. (Box-folder 105/11)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [19] leaves, Film version (Box-folder 105/11)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves, Published version (Box-folder 105/11)
    - Lazy
      - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf, At top: second number (Box-folder 105/12)
    - Let's say it with firecrackers see also The fourth of July vocal routine
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 105/13)
      - Negative photocopy of printed piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 105/13)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [9] leaves (Box-folder 105/13)
    - Let's start the New Year right
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 105/14)
      - Sketch of piano score; [2] p. (Box-folder 105/14)
      - Sketch of lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 105/14)
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p. (Box-folder 105/14)
      - Photocopy of manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p. (Box-folder 105/14)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [6] leaves (Box-folder 105/14)
    - Plenty to be thankful for
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 105/15)
      - Sketch of lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 105/15)
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score(2); 4 p. each (Box-folder 105/15)
      - Photocopies of printed piano-vocal score(2); 6 p. each (Box-folder 105/15)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [20] leaves (Box-folder 105/15)
    - Song of freedom see also The fourth of July vocal routine
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [11] leaves (Box-folder 105/16)
    - This is a great country, Not used
      - Manuscript piano-vocal scores(7); [2, 2, 3, 3, 3, 3, 2] p. (Box-folder 105/17)
      - Sketches; 7 p. (Box-folder 105/17)
      - Mimeographs of manuscript piano-vocal score(2); 3 p. each (Box-folder 105/17)
      - Photocopy of letter to Mark Sandrich at Paramount, June 19, 1941 (Box-folder 105/17)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [27] leaves (Box-folder 105/17)
    - White Christmas
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 105/18)
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p., Laid in: manuscript correction leaf; [1] leaf (Box-folder 105/18)
      - Manuscript piano score; [2] p. (Box-folder 105/18)
      - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p., Dated: 1/8/1940; At bottom: sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 105/18)
      - Sketches; [1, 2, 4] p. (Box-folder 105/18)
      - Photocopies of piano-vocal score(2); 3 p. each (Box-folder 105/18)
      - Photocopies of holograph vocal part(2); [1] p. each (Box-folder 105/18)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves, At top: Holiday inn, 4th number (Box-folder 105/18)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] leaves, At top: January 8, 1940 (Box-folder 105/18)
      - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf, At top: Christmas (Box-folder 105/18)
    - You're easy to dance with
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [5] p., Laid in: manuscript fragment; [1] p. (Box-folder 105/19)
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [5] p. (Box-folder 105/19)
      - Sketch of piano score; [2] p. (Box-folder 105/19)
      - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 105/19)
      - Photocopy of manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 105/19)
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 105/19)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [15] p. (Box-folder 105/19)
    - Scripts
      - Holograph notes: [2] leaves, At top: Tentative layout for song book (Box-folder 105/20)
      - Holograph list of holidays: [1] leaf (Box-folder 105/20)
      - Typescript running lists; [7] leaves (Box-folder 105/20)
      - Holograph list of holidays; [1] leaf (Box-folder 106/1)
      - Holograph list of holidays; [2] leaves, At top: Happy Holiday, tentative layout for song book (Box-folder 106/1)
      - Typescript list of holidays; [1] p., Original title at top: Happy holidays (Box-folder 106/1)
      - Typescript idea and notes; 4 p. each, 2, and 1 carbon copy (Box-folder 106/1)
      - Typescript list of songs; [7] leaves (Box-folder 106/1)
      - Typescript first rough draft for a revue; [5] p., With holograph annotations; At top left: Copy of this sent to Capt. O'Brien for copyrighting, Feb. 16, 1939 (Box-folder 106/1)
      - Carbon copies of complete typescript version of above; [6] p. each, On cover: Feb. 16, 1939 (Box-folder 106/1)
      - Carbon copy of typed "notes on Holiday inn"; 3 p. each, Blue folder; and carbon copy, no folder (Box-folder 106/2)
      - Carbon copy of typed "notes on conferences..., April 21, 1941; 9 p. (Box-folder 106/2)
      - Carbon copy of typed "notes on conferences..., April 28, 1941; 31 p. each, 2 copies, blue folder (Box-folder 106/2)
      - Carbon copy of typed script; [35] p., Unbound; On cover: 8/29/41 (Box-folder 106/3)
      - Carbon copy of typed script; [20] p., Blue folder; On cover: Revisions in latter portion, Sept. 27, 1941 (Box-folder 106/3)
      - Carbon copy of typed script; [164] p., Black spring binder; On cover: Oct. 14, 1941 (Box-folder 106/3)
      - Carbon copy of typed script; [51] p., Yellow paper, unbound; At top: Oct. 18, 1941, #8462, Sequence B (Box-folder 106/4)
      - Mimeograph copy of typed script; [122] p., Bound by paper fasteners (Box-folder 106/5)
      - Mimeograph copy of typed script; [16] p., No cover, bound by staple; At top: Sequence E; Dated: 12/15/41 (Box-folder 106/5)
  - Irving Berlin musical, Unproduced
    - Typescript screenplay; 25 p. (Box-folder 219/23)
  - The last resorts see also Wise guy, Unproduced, 1952; Alternate title: Palm beach; Apparently based on Cleveland Amory’s 1952 book, Last resorts, this was the first of Berlin’s two attempts to write a musical about brothers Wilson and Addison Mizner; the second attempt, 4 years later, was based on Alva Johnson’s The legendary Mizners, and first entitled Sentimental guy, and later, Wise guy.
    - Sittin' in the sun (counting my money) see also Non-show music (Box-folder 107/1)
      - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf
    - The snobs on the wrong side of the track see also Wise guy (Box-folder 107/2)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves
    - The top 400 people (Box-folder 107/3)
      - Holograph lyric sheets; [2] leaves
    - Typescript outlines of Act I; [12] leaves (Box-folder 107/4)
    - Typescript list of possible songs for Palm Beach; [3] leaves (Box-folder 107/4)
  - Liberty hall, Unproduced, 1943
    - Carbon copy of notes; 2 p., Stapled; At top: notes on story idea (Box-folder 219/24)
    - Typed script; 8 p. each, 1 ribbon, 1 carbon copy (Box-folder 219/24)
    - Typed script; 9 p., 2 staples at top; At top: On train conference Liberty hall (Box-folder 219/24)
    - Carbon copy of typescript treatment; 49 p., On t.p.: 7/21/43 (Box-folder 219/24)
  - Louisiana purchase, Stage, 1940
    - Scores and parts
      - Bound manuscript condensed score; around 100 p. (Box-folder 107/5)
      - Bound printed piano-vocal scores(2); [60] p. each (Box-folder 108/1)
      - Apologia
        - Part one: The letter, Alternate title: Opening letter
          - Full score: Opening letter #1, 22 p. (Box-folder 7/1)
          - Photocopies of piano-vocal score; p. 2-6, 2-3 (Box-folder 108/2)
          - Typescript lyric sheets; [9] leaves (Box-folder 108/2)
        - Part two: It's news to us (Opening), Alternate title: Opening Chorus-It's news to us
          - Full score: Opening chorus, 43 p., At top: extra material; Laid in: Opening chorus-new introduction; [1] p.; Laid in: Opening chorus-newer introduction #2; [1] p.; Laid in: End of opening chorus; 6 p. (Box-folder 7/2)
          - Full score: Opening chorus #2, letter K, 11 p. (Box-folder 7/2)
          - Full score: Opening chorus-new dance, 6 p. (Box-folder 7/2)
          - Photocopies of piano-vocal score; [6, 6] p., p. 9-13 (Box-folder 108/3)
          - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 108/3)
          - Sketch of piano score; 5 p. (Box-folder 108/3)
          - Typescript lyric sheets; [9] leaves (Box-folder 108/3)
          - Manuscript and photocopy orchestral parts (Box-folder 111/9)
      - Cake-walk; 41 p. (Box-folder 7/3)
      - Chimes #27A; [1] p. (Box-folder 7/4)
      - Dance with me (tonight at the Mardi Gras) see also Skate with me from As thousands cheer, Alternate title: Tonight at the masquerade
        - Full score #9, Folder only (Box-folder 7/5)
        - Full score: Waltz; [87] p. (Box-folder 7/6)
        - Full score: Reprise #13A, Folder only (Box-folder 7/7)
        - Full score: Strings only; 5 p. (Box-folder 7/8)
        - Vocal score; [20] p. (Box-folder 12/1)
        - Vocal score; 5 p., At top: insert for 3rd chorus (D major) (Box-folder 12/1)
        - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 108/4)
        - Photocopy/manuscript piano-vocal score; [7] p. (Box-folder 108/4)
        - Photocopies of piano-vocal score(2); [5] p. each (Box-folder 108/4)
        - Photocopies of printed piano-vocal score; p. 34-37, 36-37 (Box-folder 108/4)
        - Photocopy of printed piano-vocal score; [7] p., With annotations (Box-folder 108/4)
        - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 108/4)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 108/4)
        - Orchestral parts: La valsette (Box-folder 110/6)
        - Orchestral parts: Cover (Box-folder 110/7)
        - Orchestral parts: Reprise (Box-folder 110/8)
      - Entr'acte, Alternate title: New York Entr'acte
        - Full score #18; 4 p. (Box-folder 7/9)
        - Full score #18; 7 p. (Box-folder 7/9)
      - Finale Act I
        - Full score #17; [20] p. (Box-folder 7/10)
        - Full score #17; 44 p. (Box-folder 7/10)
        - Full score; 6 p. (Box-folder 7/10)
        - Vocal score; 2 p. (Box-folder 12/2)
        - Photocopy/manuscript piano-vocal score; [10] p. (Box-folder 108/5)
        - Photocopy of printed/manuscript piano-vocal score; [9] p. (Box-folder 108/5)
        - Typed script; [2] p. (Box-folder 108/5)
        - Orchestral parts (Box-folder 110/9)
      - Finale Act II
        - Manuscript short score; [10] p. (Box-folder 108/6)
        - Photocopy of manuscript short score; [2] p. (Box-folder 108/6)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [9] leaves, Some with holograph annotations (Box-folder 108/6)
        - Orchestral parts (Box-folder 110/10)
      - Finale ultimo
        - Full score #33; 21 p. (Box-folder 8/1)
        - Full score #33; [35] p. (Box-folder 8/1)
        - Full score; [1] p. (Box-folder 8/2)
        - Full score: New end; 5 p. (Box-folder 8/2)
      - Fools fall in love
        - Full score #26; 49 p. (Box-folder 8/3)
        - Full score #16, Folder only (Box-folder 8/3)
        - Full score: Stage hands music; 9 p., At top: change (Box-folder 8/3)
        - Vocal score #26; 3 p. (Box-folder 12/3)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal scores(2); [3] p. each (Box-folder 108/7)
        - Sketches; [3] p. (Box-folder 108/7)
        - Photocopies of piano-vocal score; [4, 8] p. (Box-folder 108/7)
        - Photocopy of printed piano-vocal score; p. 54-57 (Box-folder 108/7)
        - Photocopy of printed piano-vocal score; p. 54-57, At top: #13 (Box-folder 108/7)
        - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 108/7)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 108/7)
        - Sheet music (Box-folder 108/7)
        - Orchestral parts (Box-folder 110/11)
      - I'd love to be shot out of a cannon with you, Alternate title: I'd love to be shot from a cannon with you; Dropped after tryout
        - Full score #23; 46 p. (Box-folder 8/4)
        - Full score; [1] p., At top: New 2 bars from "C" (last 2) to "H" (Box-folder 8/4)
        - Full score; 9 p. (Box-folder 8/5)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 108/8)
        - Sketches; [6] p. (Box-folder 108/8)
        - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 108/8)
      - I'm a Quaker's daughter from the Latin quarter see Music box revue, 1939 and Non-show music, Not used
      - It'll come to you, Dropped during tryout
        - Full score; 11 p. (Box-folder 8/6)
        - Full score: Introduction; [27] p. (Box-folder 8/7)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p. (Box-folder 108/9)
        - Photocopies of manuscript piano-vocal score(2); [4] p. each (Box-folder 108/9)
        - Photocopies of manuscript piano-vocal (conductor's) score; [4, 3] p. (Box-folder 108/9)
        - Photocopy of printed piano-vocal score; [4] p. (Box-folder 108/9)
        - Photocopy of printed piano-vocal score (last p. manuscript); [5] p. (Box-folder 108/9)
        - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 108/9)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [8] leaves (Box-folder 108/9)
        - Sheet music (Box-folder 108/9)
        - Orchestral parts (Box-folder 111/1)
      - It's a lovely day tomorrow
        - Full score; 9 p. (Box-folder 9/1)
        - Full score; 6 p., Laid in: insert, p. 2 only (Box-folder 13/1)
        - Full score: Introduction #6, #7; [1] p. (Box-folder 9/2)
        - Full score: Vocal; 20 p. (Box-folder 9/2)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal scores; [2, 3] p. (Box-folder 109/1)
        - Sketches; [5] p. (Box-folder 109/1)
        - Photocopies of printed piano-vocal score(2); [3] p. each, With annotations (Box-folder 109/1)
        - Photocopies of printed piano-vocal score(2); [4] p. each, Laid in copy 2: manuscript piano-vocal score; [1] p. (Box-folder 109/1)
        - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal scores(2); 4 p. each (Box-folder 109/1)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [12] leaves (Box-folder 109/1)
        - Sheet music (Box-folder 109/1)
        - Orchestral parts (Box-folder 111/2)
      - Latins know how
        - Full score: #21; 19 p. (Box-folder 9/3)
        - Full score: #21; [38] p. (Box-folder 9/3)
        - Full score: Verse, alternate #15; 3 p. (Box-folder 9/4)
        - Full score: Chorus, change #22; 15 p. (Box-folder 9/4)
        - Full score: Chorus, change #22; 8 p. (Box-folder 9/4)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., No lyric (Box-folder 109/2)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal scores(2); [6] p. each (Box-folder 109/2)
        - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 109/2)
        - Photocopies of piano-vocal score(2); [6] p. each (Box-folder 109/2)
        - Photocopy/manuscript piano-vocal (conductor's) score; [11] p., No lyric (Box-folder 109/2)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 109/2)
        - Orchestral parts (Box-folder 111/3)
      - The Lord done fixed up my soul
        - Full score #24; 65 p. (Box-folder 9/5)
        - Full score #24; 32 p. (Box-folder 9/5)
        - Full score: Ride out, new; 2 p. (Box-folder 9/5)
        - Full score #15; 58 p., Laid in: Finale I; 10 p.; On inside back cover: manuscript fragments (Box-folder 9/6)
        - Full score: For stage hands; chorus, change; 13 p. (Box-folder 9/7)
        - Full score: Vocally; 41 p. (Box-folder 9/7)
        - Full score: Vocally; p. 1-4 (Box-folder 9/7)
        - Vocal score; 28 p. (Box-folder 12/4)
        - Vocal score: Interlude, end of chorale; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/4)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal scores; [2, 4] p. (Box-folder 109/3)